Guide to the Les Dames d'Escoffier New York Archive, 1976-2014 MSS.150
Fales Library and Special Collections
Les Dames d'Escoffier New York Archive
1976-2014
Fales Library and Special Collections
Les Dames d'Escoffier, New York
MSS.150
16.5 Linear Feet in 29 boxes
Les Dames d'Escoffier New York (LDENY) is a society of professional women involved in the food, wine, and hospitality industries. The purpose of the organization is to support and promote the understanding, appreciation, and knowledge of food, beverages, nutrition, the arts of the table, and other fields as they relate to these disciplines. The collection includes menus, flyers, invitation cards, members' correspondence, administrative and promotional material, photographs, and videorecordings.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Archive was donated to the Fales Library by Lila Gault, on behalf of Les Dames d'Escoffier New York in October 2003. Additional donations were made in 2007, 2008, and 2016. Materials in 2016 Accretion - Series XII: Unprocessed Materials were donated by Margaret Happel Perry, Past President of Les Dames d'Escoffier New York, in 2016. The accession number associated with this gift is 2016.020.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Historical Note
Les Dames d'Escoffier, New York (LDENY), is a society of professional women involved in the food, wine, and hospitality industries. It was founded in honor of Auguste Escoffier, whom Les Dames' mission statement credits with having "single-handedly brought the culinary art into the modern era." Escoffier "elevated the role of cooks from that of laborers to artists;" when he died, he "left the world a new art, that of dining." Les Dames d'Escoffier was founded in New York in 1976. With expansion to other cities, Les Dames d'Escoffier International (LDEI) was formed in 1985 to operate as an umbrella organization. Membership is by invitation only and exclusive to women who have distinguished themselves in the respective fields with which Les Dames is concerned. Les Dames organizes various food-related activities throughout the year, the majority of which are dinners; new members are inducted during the "annual gala dinners." Les Dames' major philanthropic activity consists of promoting the education and advancement of women in careers related to food industries. The society provides scholarships for women desiring to become professionals or to advance their skills in the fields of food, wine, other beverages, nutrition, the arts of the table and related disciplines.
Scope and Content Note
The Les Dames d'Escoffier New York Archive spans the organization's activities from the years 1976-2014. Organizing and enjoying elaborate dinners constitutes the primary activity of Les Dames d'Escoffier, and Series I contains the dinner menus, flyers, invitation cards and more miscellaneous materials that these events generated. Also included in Series I are materials relating to "dinner events" with the emphasis on "event" rather than "dinner," in other words wine and/or food tastings, picnics, brunches and other food-related activities of the organization.
The collection includes dinner menus, invitation cards, and promotional materials, for example, press releases and newspaper clippings, from various dinner events organized by Les Dames d'Escoffier, New York. The collection also includes the correspondence of individual LDENY members, as well as correspondence from individuals and institutions connected with the organization. The collection also includes the Les Dames d'Escoffier newsletter "Journal," as well as several issues of "Reporter," the newsletter produced by LDENY's umbrella organization, Les Dames d'Escoffier International. Administrative material generated by the day-to-day activities of running an organization, such as meeting minutes and financial statements are also included in the collection. Visual documentation of events in the form of photographs and videorecordings are also included. Almost every series in the collection contains both Les Dames d'Escoffier New York and Les Dames d'Escoffier International material; the LDENY material has been grouped toward the beginning of each series and the LDEI material toward the end of each series. Oversize material from each of the series is described at the end of the finding aid.
Series Description
Series I: LDENY Dinner Events.
Series I contains the dinner menus, flyers, invitation cards and various other materials generated by the dinner events organized by LDENY. Also included in the series are "dinner events" with the emphasis on "event" rather than "dinner," in other words wine and/or food tastings, picnics, brunches and other food-related activities. Subseries A contains LDEI Dinner Events-material
Series II: Annual Gala Dinners.
Series II consists of the dinner menus, flyers, invitation cards and various other materials generated by the annual gala dinners organized by LDENY. During these events, new members were inducted into the organization.
Series III: Salute to Women in Gastronomy Week, 1994.
Series III contains the dinner menus, flyers, invitation cards, promotional and administrative material generated by the "Salute to Women in Gastronomy Week, 1994," a week-long series of culinary arts events organized by LDENY in 1994. The "Week" was designed to celebrate and promote the presence of women in gastronomy.
Series IV: Classes, Lectures and Conferences.
Series IV contains the class packets, conference folders, survey forms, findings and reports handed out during various such events organized by LDENY.
Series V: Correspondence.
Series V contains LDENY members' correspondence, as well as that of other people variously connected with the organization. Individual correspondents' letters have been arranged alphabetically, last names first. In cases where only one item of correspondence issued from a particular correspondent, the item in question was placed, along with other similar items, in one folder. In the case of multiple items issuing from the same correspondent, these were placed in a single folder bearing the name of the correspondent. Subseries A contains letters with collective addressees (Ex., "Dear Dame(s)..."). Subseries B contains memos. Subseries C contains letters written to and from Les Dames members on the topic of the Membership Roster of 1984, subseries D on the topic of the Les Dames' scholarships, and subseries E on the topic of the Les Dames' Dinner Events.
Series VI: Newsletters.
Series VI contains the LDENY newsletter, entitled "Journal," spanning the years from 1976-2000. Subseries A contains the LDEI newsletter, "Reporter," spanning the years 1989-2002. Newsletters from organizations linked with Les Dames, such as Les Amis d'Escoffier, have been filed within this series as well, and are located toward the end of Subseries A.
Series VII: Administrative Material.
Series VII contains general information about Les Dames d'Escoffier, such as mission statements, organizational history, and biographical material about Auguste Escoffier. It also contains material relevant to the everyday administration of the organization, such as by-laws. These have been filed chronologically and grouped under the heading Subseries A. Subseries B contains material specific to membership in the organization, including membership directories. Subseries C contains material specific to the Les Dames' scholarships. Subseries D contains miscellaneous administrative material, such as financial reports and letterheads, as well as informational material distributed by some of the culinary organizations and museums with which LDENY was involved. Subseries E contains material related to the LDENY Expansion Committee which administered the addition of new chapters to the organization.
Series VIII: Board Meetings.
Series VIII contains LDENY Board Meeting minutes and committee reports. Subseries A contains the same material, but from LDEI board meetings.
Series IX: Binders.
Series IX consists of material originally filed by LDENY members into binders. The material is primarily administrative (board meetings, etc.), but it also includes members' correspondence and material relating to Les Dames' dinner events.
Series X: Publicity
Series X consists of publicity materials, such as newspaper clippings, press releases, a visitor's book, as well as photographs, negatives, and slides. The latter largely portray Les Dames' scholarship winners and ceremonies, as well as Les Dames dinner events.
Series XI: Objects and Media
Series XI consists of LDENY commemorative objects and media consisting of three video recordings of LDENY events.
Series XII: Accretion 2016: Unprocessed Materials
Series XII consists of materials relating to the philanthropic, organizational, and social activities of the society. Materials include CDs and floppy disk, membership directories, newsletters and journals, meeting minutes, fundraising event planning materials, and DVD records of the activities of the presidents of the society from 2011-2014.
Arrangement
Files are grouped into twelve series. With the exception of Series V and XII, materials are arranged chronologically. Each series, with the exception of II, V, X and XI, contain material from both the New York-chapter of Les Dames d'Escoffier (LDENY), as well as its "umbrella organization", Les Dames d'Escoffier International (LDEI). Within each series heading, LDENY material has been filed toward the beginning, and LDEI material toward the end of the series, sometimes as a separate subseries. Series XII has not been arranged by an archivist.
Series List:
Series I: LDENY Dinner Events
Series II: Annual Gala Dinners
Series III: Salute to Women in Gastronomy Week, 1994
Series IV: Classes, Lectures and Conferences
Series V: Correspondence
Series VI: Newsletters
Series VII: Administrative Material
Series VIII: Board Meetings
Series IX: Binders
Series X: Publicity
Series XI: Objects/Artifacts and Media
Oversize - Series I: LDENY Dinner Events
Oversize - Series II: Annual Gala Dinners
Oversize - Series III: Salute to Women in Gastronomy Week, 1994
Accretion 2007 - Series I: LDENY Dinner Events
Accretion 2007 - Series V: Correspondence
Accretion 2007 - Series VI: Newsletters
Accretion 2007 - Series VII: Administrative Material
Accretion 2007 - Series VIII: Board Meetings
Accretion 2007 - Series IX: Binders
Accretion 2008 - Series I: LDENY Dinner Events
Accretion 2008 - Series II: Annual Gala Dinners
Accretion 2008 - Series V: Correspondence
Accretion 2008 - Series VI: Newsletters
Accretion 2008 - Series VII: Administrative Material
Accretion 2008 - Series VIII: Board Meetings
Accretion 2016 - Series XII
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
Cecily Brownstone Papers (MSS.134)
Cecily Brownstone Collection of American Cookery (A related name search in Bobcat, NYU's library catalog, under "Cecily Brownstone" will retrieve records for the entire library, consisting of over 8400 titles.)
Separated Material
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
New York (N.Y.).; Minutes (administrative records); Videocassettes.; Newsletters.; Fliers (printed matter); Promotional materials; Cooking, American -- History -- 20th century.; Visitors' books.; Bylaws (administrative records); Photographs.; Food industry and trade; Invitations.; Women |z United States |x Societies and Clubs.; Women cooks -- United States.; Slides (photographs); Women cooks |z United States |x History |y 20th century.; Dinners and dining -- United States -- History.; Dinners and dining -- New York.; Gastronomy.; Menus.; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Culinary industry.; Cooks -- United States; Cooks -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Barbour, Beverly, 1927-; Kinard, Malvina C.; Les Dames d'Escoffier International; Les Dames d'Escoffier, New York; Lyons, Mary E.; Pate-Green, Penelope; Schur, Sylvia; Studley, Helen; Yonkers, Ann; Bartholomew, Patricia S.; Bastianich, Lidia; Brock, Carol; Chalmers, Irena; Child, Julia; Escoffier, A. (Auguste), 1846-1935; Hanle, Zack, 1918-; Hazelton, Nika Standen
- Series I: LDENY Dinner Events
  Scope and Contents note
  Series I contains the dinner menus, flyers, invitation cards and other materials generated by the dinner events organized by LDENY. Included in the series are also food tastings, picnics, (cook)book parties, and other food-related activities.
  - Subseries A: LDENY Dinner Events
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - LDENY Dinner Events 1986: Statue of Liberty Dinner (Oct) (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - LDENY Dinner Events: Culinary Olympics, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - LDENY Dinner Events: "Dames Who Drink", 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - LDENY Dinner Events, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Subseries A: LDEI Dinner Events
    - LDEI Dinner Events: Washington D.C. Chapter, 1982-1996 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - LDEI Dinner Events: Misc. Chapters, 1989-1996 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - LDEI Dinner Events: Anniversary Dinners, 1991/1994/1999 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - LDEI Dinner Events: A Taste of Sicily, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - LDEI Dinner Events: MFK Fisher Award Luncheon, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - LDEI Dinner Events: Les Amis d'Escoffier, La Fondation d'Escoffier, 1991-2000 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Series II: Annual Gala Dinners
      Series II consists of the dinner menus, flyers, invitation cards and other material generated by Les Dames' annual gala dinners.
      - LDENY Investiture of New Members Dinner, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - LDENY First Gala Dinner, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 47)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 50)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 51)
      - Series III: Salute to Women in Gastronomy Week, 1994
        Series III contains the dinner menus, flyers, invitation cards, promotional and administrative material generated by the "Salute to Women in Gastronomy Week, 1994," a week-long series of gastronomy-related events organized by LDENY in 1994. The "Week" was designed to celebrate and promote the presence of women in gastronomy.
        - Promotional Material, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 53)
        - Organizing Costs, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 54)
        - Committee Reports, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 55)
        - Gala Auction Donation Forms, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 56)
        - Event: Changing Careers, January 18, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 57)
        - Event: Females in the Professional Kitchen, January 19, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 58)
        - Event: Edible Art, January 20, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 59)
        - Event: Food Film Forum, January 22, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 60)
        - Event: Les Plaisir des Dames, Gala Auction and Dinner, January 23, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 61)
        - Event: Les Plaisir des Dames Dinner Menus, January 23, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 62)
        - Event: Les Plaisir des Dames Table Arrangements, January 23, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 63)
        - Event: LDEI Authors, January 17-23, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 64)
      - LDENY Annual Gala Dinner, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Series IV: Classes, Lectures and Conferences
  Series IV contains the class packets, conference folders, survey forms, findings and reports handed out during various classes, lectures and symposia organized by LDENY.
  - Lecture: Culinary Symposium on Food in 2010, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Lecture: Making it Big in Food Media, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Master Classes (class folder), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Master Classes (class folder), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Future Food Survey Forms, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Future Food Survey Findings (report), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Future Food: Conference Packet (1), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Future Food: Conference Packet (2), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Future Food: Conference Packet (3), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Future Food: Logistics, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 74)
- Series V: Correspondence
  Series V contains LDENY members' correspondence, as well as that of other people variously connected with the organization. The correspondence of individual correspondents has been arranged alphabetically, last name(s) first. In cases where only one item of correspondence issued from a particular correspondent, the item in question was placed, along with other similar items, in one folder. In the case of multiple items issuing from the same correspondent, these were placed in a single folder bearing the name of the correspondent. Subseries A contains letters with collective addressees (Ex., "Dear Dame(s)..."). Subseries B contains memos. Subseries C contains letters written to and from Les Dames members on the topic of the Membership Roster of 1984, subseries D on the topic of the Les Dames' scholarships, and subseries E on the topic of the Les Dames' Dinner Events.
  - Alpert, S. - Andoh, E., 1990-2000 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Bachal, A. - Briand, J., 1976-2000 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Barbour, Beverley, 1981-1996 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Bartholomew, Pat, 1989-2000 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Bayrock, Jean, 1991-1999 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Brock, Carol, 1978/1990 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Buckner, Dorothy, 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Chalmers, Irena, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Coe, A. - Cowley, C., 1983-2000 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Cutler, Carol, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Dannenbaum, J. - Fife, B., 1981-1997 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Frank, Charlotte (NY Board of Education), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Freeman, Andrew (Russian Tea Room), 1989 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Ganter, B. - Gregorian, V., 1982-2000 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Gold, Rozanne, 1983-1994 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Griffin, Mary Ellen, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Halper, J. - Jantzen, L., 1984-1992 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Hanle, Zack, 1984-1999 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Jacobson, Ruth, 1985-1993 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Kesten, R. - Libbey, J., 1983-1994 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Kinard, Malvina, 1982-1991 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - King, Patricia (Schlesinger Library, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Kirsch, Abigail, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Low, Frances, 1986-1991 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Lyons, Mary, 1982-1989 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Marchand Ass. - Muela, M., 1982-2000 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Martel, Priscilla, 1991-2000 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Nestle, M. - O'Neill, M., 1989 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Palanci, M., 1990-1999 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Palmer, C. - Pitts, E., 1983-1990 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Pate-Green, Penelope, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Ross, R. - Suprenant, V., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Sass, Lorna, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Schur, Sylvia, 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Singer, Niki, 1983-1989 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Stern, Margaret, 1983-1990 (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Steves, Gale, 1988-2000 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Studley, Helen, 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Told, W. - Type, N., 1986-1990 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Van Loon, J. - Zara, L., 1982-2000 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Yonkers, Ann, 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Misc. unidentified correspondents, undated (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Subseries A: Letters with collective addressees
    - Letters with collective addressees, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Letters with collective addressees, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Letters with collective addressees, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Letters with collective addressees, 1989-1993 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Letters with collective addressees, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Letters with collective addressees, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Subseries B: Memos
    - Memos, 1976-1987 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Memos, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Memos, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Memos, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Memos, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Memos, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Memos, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Memos, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Subseries C: Membership Roster
    - Membership Roster A-K, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Membership Roster K-Z, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Subseries D: Scholarship
    - Scholarship, 1977-1984 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Scholarship, 1985-1989 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Scholarship, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - Scholarship, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - Scholarship, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Subseries E: Dinner Events
    - Dinner Events: Culinary Olympics, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - Women in Gastronomy Week, 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - Women in Gastronomy Week, 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 141)
- Series VI: Newsletters
  Series VI contains the Les Dames d'Escoffier, New York newsletter, entitled "Journal" (1976-2002). Subseries A contains the Les Dames d'Escoffier International newsletter, "Reporter" (1989-2002). Newsletters from organizations linked with Les Dames, such as Les Amis d'Escoffier, have been filed within this subseries heading.
  - LDENY Newsletter, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - LDENY Newsletter, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - LDENY Newsletter, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - LDENY Newsletter, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 145)
  - LDENY Newsletter, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 146)
  - LDENY Newsletter, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - LDENY Newsletter, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - LDENY Newsletter, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - LDENY Newsletter, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - LDENY Newsletter, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - LDENY Newsletter, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - LDENY Newsletter, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - LDENY Newsletter, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - LDENY Newsletter, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 155)